<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on InnoTep Research Group</title><link>https://innotep.github.io/en/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on InnoTep Research Group</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://innotep.github.io/en/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Proyecto de Aprendizaje-Servicio (ApS) - GADES</title><link>https://innotep.github.io/en/projects/aps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innotep.github.io/en/projects/aps/</guid><description>This project aims to validate and improve Gades: a technological solution to support education professionals in identifying language problems in children, a website for assessing language and communication in children aged 0 to 6, through the collaboration of an undergraduate student.</description></item><item><title>Certified Innovation Path: FELL Programme</title><link>https://innotep.github.io/en/projects/fell/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innotep.github.io/en/projects/fell/</guid><description>Development of courses on cybersecurity in the field of digital health and clinical data.</description></item><item><title>PLATA</title><link>https://innotep.github.io/en/projects/plata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innotep.github.io/en/projects/plata/</guid><description>The objective of the PLATA project is to develop educational prototypes to digitise the editorial collection of the UDIT Student Residence so that it can be used as teaching material in secondary schools, sixth form colleges and universities, both for classroom use and for independent research work at all levels, including final degree projects and doctoral theses. The project offers the opportunity to digitise the editorial collection in a modern and durable interactive format in line with the current uses of new generations, facilitating consultation and reading through interactive technologies, cloud file consultation and artificial intelligence.</description></item><item><title>SmartDiabetes</title><link>https://innotep.github.io/en/projects/smartdiabetes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innotep.github.io/en/projects/smartdiabetes/</guid><description>SMARTDIABETES solution enhances diabetes care through a data-driven digital ecosystem. It integrates the SocialDiabetes tool for patient self-management and remote monitoring across three clinical sites. The project creates a value-based healthcare reimbursement model and delivers a comprehensive operating blueprint for healthcare organizations, including care pathways, user support, and training strategies. By prioritizing adoption, acceptance, and sustainability, SMARTDIABETES puts patients and care providers at the center, ensuring long-term impact through collaboration among clinical, academic, and business experts.</description></item><item><title>TEACH ME: A GAMING SOLUTION TO SUPPORT THE TREATMENT OF CHILDREN WITH AUTISM SPECTRUM DISORDER</title><link>https://innotep.github.io/en/projects/teachme/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innotep.github.io/en/projects/teachme/</guid><description>Development of serious toys for therapy for children with autism</description></item><item><title>Value</title><link>https://innotep.github.io/en/projects/value/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innotep.github.io/en/projects/value/</guid><description>The VALUE solution helps turn digital health transformation into reality. Defeating patient disease and restoring patient health is the dominant concept driving healthcare delivery in most facilities. The growing prevalence of chronic diseases among the population is jeopardising the sustainability of the current healthcare system. VALUE is a solution aimed at healthcare providers to deliver healthcare services that provide value to patients while maintaining sustainable healthcare.</description></item><item><title>Ubiquitous Detection, Attention and Early Stimulation Ecosystem for Children with Developmental Disorders</title><link>https://innotep.github.io/en/projects/educere/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innotep.github.io/en/projects/educere/</guid><description>Development of smart toys for detecting motor disorders in children.</description></item></channel></rss>